<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on Portfolio Website and Blog</title>
    <link>https://mohammedrashithkp.github.io/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on Portfolio Website and Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://mohammedrashithkp.github.io/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://mohammedrashithkp.github.io/blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mohammedrashithkp.github.io/blog/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to My Blog! Welcome to my personal blog! Here, I share posts on various topics including tech, development, robotics, and other areas of interest. You&amp;rsquo;ll find tutorials, guides, updates on personal projects, and musings about new tools and technologies that I explore.
In my blog, I cover topics such as:
 Setting up development environments Exploring new tools like Kitty and Yazi  Stay tuned for more posts, and feel free to explore my articles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://mohammedrashithkp.github.io/blog/categries/tech-tutorials/kitty-yazi-setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mohammedrashithkp.github.io/blog/categries/tech-tutorials/kitty-yazi-setup/</guid>
      <description>Setting Up Kitty and Yazi in Ubuntu Kitty and Yazi are two powerful tools for making your terminal experience in Ubuntu more efficient and visually appealing. This guide will walk you through installing and setting them up.
What You&amp;rsquo;ll Need Before you begin, ensure that you have the following:
 A working installation of Ubuntu (this guide assumes Ubuntu 20.04 or newer) A terminal to execute commands  Step 1: Install Kitty Kitty is a GPU-based terminal emulator that’s fast and highly customizable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://mohammedrashithkp.github.io/blog/categries/tech-tutorials/linux-installation-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mohammedrashithkp.github.io/blog/categries/tech-tutorials/linux-installation-guide/</guid>
      <description>A Beginner&amp;rsquo;s Guide to Installing Linux Linux is an open-source operating system that powers everything from personal computers to servers and smartphones. If you&amp;rsquo;re new to Linux, installing it might seem a bit intimidating, but it&amp;rsquo;s actually easier than you think. This guide will walk you through the steps to install Linux on your computer.
What You&amp;rsquo;ll Need Before you begin, make sure you have the following:
 A computer with at least 2GB of RAM and 20GB of free storage A USB drive with at least 4GB of space (for creating a bootable installer) A stable internet connection (for downloading the Linux distribution) Backup of your important files (if you are installing Linux alongside your current OS, you might need to repartition your hard drive)  Step 1: Choose Your Linux Distribution There are many different &amp;ldquo;flavors&amp;rdquo; or distributions of Linux.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
