<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pages on Mohammed Rashith KP</title>
    <link>https://mohammedrashithkp.github.io/pages/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pages on Mohammed Rashith KP</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language><atom:link href="https://mohammedrashithkp.github.io/pages/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://mohammedrashithkp.github.io/pages/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mohammedrashithkp.github.io/pages/about/</guid>
      
      <description>Location: Malappuram, Kerala, India
About Me I am a Mechanical Engineering undergraduate at NIT Calicut, specializing in robotics, Python programming, and Linux systems. With over a year of experience leading technical teams in robotics projects, I am currently enhancing my project management skills through the Google Project Management Specialization and developing a Space Invaders Game. Passionate about applying cutting-edge technologies to real-world problems.
Education: B.Tech in Mechanical Engineering, NIT Calicut (2022–2026) Skills: Python, Linux, ROS2, Docker, Flask, Git, Machine Learning, Web Development, Project Management Current Focus: Game Development, Robotics, Project Management Core Competencies Area Proficiency Relevant Projects &amp;amp; Tools Programming Advanced Python, Bash, C++, Docker, Flask Robotics &amp;amp; Simulation Intermediate ROS2, Gazebo, Rviz2, SolidWorks, Ansys Web Development Intermediate HTML, CSS, Flask, GitHub Actions, MySQL ,Hugo Machine Learning Beginner PyTorch, Scikit-learn, Pandas, TensorFlow Project Management Intermediate Asana, Git, Google Project Management Technologies &amp;amp; Tools Languages: Python, C++, Bash, Dart, HTML, CSS Tools: Docker, Git, MySQL, SQLite, OpenCV, TensorFlow, PyTorch Development: Flask, Figma, Flutter, ROS2, MATLAB, Qt Professional Experience Role Organization Duration Responsibilities Technical Team Member Robotics Interest Group, NIT Calicut 2023–Present - Contributed to robotics projects using Ansys and ROS2.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Certifications</title>
      <link>https://mohammedrashithkp.github.io/pages/certifications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mohammedrashithkp.github.io/pages/certifications/</guid>
      
      <description> Project Initiation: Starting a Successful Project – Google, Coursera, 2024 Foundations in Project Management – Google, Coursera, 2024 Python for Everybody Specialization – University of Michigan, Coursera, 2023 MathWorks Onramp Certifications: MATLAB, Simulink, Stateflow, Image Processing </description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://mohammedrashithkp.github.io/pages/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mohammedrashithkp.github.io/pages/projects/</guid>
      
      <description>DRL Based SnakeGame:Made a Deep Reinforcement Learning Model to interact with Pygame Environment to learn the Snake game in Python using Pytorch and Pygame Space Invaders Arcade Game:Made a Classic arcade style shooter game developed in Python using Pygame Library. Elephant Quadruped Robot: Made Static and Fatigue Analysis of a single quadruped leg under half load and full load conditions using Ansys Structural Mechanical. Fingerprint Attendance System: Made Streamlit app for displaying and Filtering the attendence data from the Rasberry Pi 3B .</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
