<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Mohammed Rashith KP</title><link>https://mohammedrashithkp.github.io/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Mohammed Rashith KP</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-gb</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 00:56:05 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mohammedrashithkp.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Git &amp; Github Beginner Routines Cheat Sheet</title><link>https://mohammedrashithkp.github.io/posts/git-and-github-survival-guide/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 00:56:05 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://mohammedrashithkp.github.io/posts/git-and-github-survival-guide/</guid><description>🚀 Git &amp;amp; GitHub Beginner Routines Cheat Sheet 🟢 Routine 1: First-Time Setup Step Command Install tools sudo apt-get install git gh curl -y Set username git config --global user.name &amp;quot;your_username&amp;quot; Set email git config --global user.email &amp;quot;your_email@example.com&amp;quot; Login to GitHub gh auth login
Follow prompts in terminal &amp;amp; browser 🟢 Routine 2: Cloning Repositories Type Command Public repo git clone https://github.com/username/repository.git Private repo gh repo clone username/repository List branches git branch -a Switch branch git checkout branch-name 🟢 Routine 3: Adding a Remote to an Existing Project Step Command Add remote origin git remote add origin https://github.</description></item><item><title>Resolve GRUB Rescue and Boot into Windows</title><link>https://mohammedrashithkp.github.io/posts/resolve-grub-rescue-and-boot-into-windows/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 01:58:30 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://mohammedrashithkp.github.io/posts/resolve-grub-rescue-and-boot-into-windows/</guid><description>Step-by-Step Guide to Resolve GRUB Rescue and Boot into Windows If you tried removing Linux and are now greeted with a black screen with &amp;ldquo;Grub Rescue&amp;rdquo; on it, don&amp;rsquo;t panic—we&amp;rsquo;ve all been there. We&amp;rsquo;ll get through it without affecting any other data by following a few simple steps.
Why This Occurred When you installed Linux, it created a folder in the main EFI partition alongside Windows. This folder pointed to the partition where Linux was installed, and when you removed Linux (likely using Windows partition tools), the computer panicked because it couldn&amp;rsquo;t find the necessary folder.</description></item><item><title>Dualboot Linux Mint 21.3</title><link>https://mohammedrashithkp.github.io/posts/dualboot-linux-mint-21.3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 01:52:41 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://mohammedrashithkp.github.io/posts/dualboot-linux-mint-21.3/</guid><description>Dualboot Linux Mint 21.3 Disclaimer: &amp;ldquo;The owner of this project, platform, or service shall not be held liable for any loss, damage, or corruption of data, whether caused by system failures, user errors, or any other unforeseen circumstances. By using this service, the user acknowledges and agrees that they are solely responsible for backing up and protecting their data. The owner makes no representations or warranties regarding the security, accuracy, or completeness of any data stored or processed through the service.</description></item><item><title>Hassle-free Ros2 Setup</title><link>https://mohammedrashithkp.github.io/posts/hassle-free-ros2-setup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 01:01:33 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://mohammedrashithkp.github.io/posts/hassle-free-ros2-setup/</guid><description>Disclaimer: &amp;ldquo;This is not an official ROS2 distribution. This is a file that installs from the official ROS2 repositories. The owner of this project, platform, or service shall not be held liable for any loss, damage, or corruption of data, whether caused by system failures, user errors, or any other unforeseen circumstances. By using this service, the user acknowledges and agrees that they are solely responsible for backing up and protecting their data.</description></item></channel></rss>